He'll read you your last rites...
Demon Cop is a horror, action film directed by Rocco Karega.
A former probationary officer who is a patient at a mental asylum escapes and prowls the city, looking for victims
whose blood may cure the blood disease he has that has turned him into a werewolf-type monster.
Professor, played by Cameron Mitchell.
Edward Thurman, played by Rocco Karega.
Maria Beniley, played by Theresa Fenneaux.
Ike Logan, played by Ray Klein.
Brian Spence, played by Tony Zotta.
Kelly Adams, played by Julia Westland.
State of Grace is a 1990 American neo-noir crime drama film directed by Phil Joanou, and
starring Sean Penn, Ed Harris, Gary Oldman, Robin Wright, John Turturro, and John C.
Written by playwright Dennis McIntyre, the film was produced by Ned Dowd, Randy
Ostrow, and Ron Rotholz, with a musical score by Ennio Morricone.
Although the film was not a box office success and its release overshadowed by that of the
similarly themed Goodfellas, it was received positively by most critics.
Shot on location in New York City, the film was inspired by
the real-life Hell's Kitchen gang, the Westies.
The tone is dark.